A Guide to the Harry Flood Byrd, Sr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series IV: Miscellaneous Topics
  - F. Speeches and Statements
    - 1. Reference File of Other People's Speeches
      - George, Walter F.: 1956 March 12, Declaration of Constitutional Principles to be presented by Senator George in the Senate and in the House of Representatives by Representative Howard W. Smith (Box Box 356)
      - Goolrick, C. O'Conor: 1928, Discussion of The Short Ballot from the Affirmative View (Box Box 356)
      - Hawes, Harry Bartow: 1930 January 19, Speech. (Folder empty when processed) (Box Box 356)
      - Lausche, Frank John: 1958 July 11, Senator's Amendment to the Housing Bill presented by Senator Lausche (Box Box 356)
      - Lewis, Fulton, Jr.: 1946 August 19, Radio Address. (Folder found empty when processed) (Box Box 356)
      - Marshall: 1961 January 17, Speech prepared for Mr. Marshall congratulating the Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company on the seventy-fifth anniversary of its founding (Box Box 356)
      - Miller, Francis Pickens: 1961 April 23, Review of book by Benj. Muse, "Virginia's Massive Resistance" (Box Box 356)
      - Morrissett, Charles H.: 1927 August 5, Address before the Virginia Bar Association, Virginia Beach (Box Box 356)
      - Morrissett, Charles H.: 1928, Statement on Proposed Amendments to the Constitution of Virginia (Box Box 356)
      - Newton, Blake Tyler: 1942, Thesis entitled "The Governor of Virginia as Business Manager" (Box Box 356)
      - Parrish, J. Scott: 1929 April 19, Speech delivered before the Virginia Social Science Association, Lynchburg, Virginia (Box Box 356)
      - Pollard, John Garland: 1934 January 10, Message delivered before the General Assembly (Box Box 356)
      - Rascob, John J.: 1929 June 10, Speech at a dinner given by the Jefferson Association of the District of Columbia (Box Box 356)
      - Reed, William T.: 1927 March 22, Statement on Changes in Automobile Taxes (Box Box 356)
      - Ridgway, Matthew B.: 1956 February 29, Address at the dedication of Virginia War Memorial at Richmond, Virginia (Box Box 356)
      - Ritchie, Governor: 1928 April 20, Address at the annual meeting of the American Society of Newspaper Editors, Washington, D. C. (Box Box 356)
      - Robertson, A. Willis: 1923 January 19, Speech at Lexington on the occasion of the Lee-Jackson Day (Box Box 356)
      - Robinson, Senator Joe: 1937 June 18, Remarks on the National Debt in U. S. Senate. (Folder empty when processed) (Box Box 356)
      - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano: 1941 January 6, President's four freedons as given in his address to Congress (Box Box 356)
      - Shouse, Jouett: 1929 June 10, Speech at Dinner given in his honor by Jefferson Democratic Association of the District of Columbia (Box Box 356)
      - Sloan, Matthew Scott: 1929, Speech, New England Society of New York (Box Box 356)
      - Sumners, Hatton W.: 1940 February 1, Speech given in the House of Representatives on the One Hundred and Fifieth Anniversary of the First Convening of the Supreme Court of the United States (Box Box 356)
      - Swank, Ward: 1927 June, Speech introducing Governor Byrd at Sam Houston Monument unveiling, Rockbridge County (Box Box 356)
      - Trinkle, E. Lee: 1922 March 3, Address delivered before a Joint Session of the General Assembly of Virginia (Box Box 356)
      - Tuck, William M.: 1946 January, Inaugural Address (Box Box 356)
      - Tuck, William M.: 1948 April 6, Radio Address (Box Box 356)
      - Welles, Sumner: 1943 October 16, Address at the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Luncheon of the Foreign Policy Association (Box Box 356)
      - Wickham, Henry T.: 1940 February 23, Address delivered before the Joint Session of the General Assembly of Virginia (Box Box 356)
      - Woodrum, Clifton A.: 1937 August 24, Radio Address (Box Box 356)
      - Congressional Record: 1946 April 26, Appropriation continuing the Joint Economy Committee (Box Box 356)
      - Communication: 1929 August 14, On Thomas Jefferson from Virginia State Library. (Folder empty when processed) (Box Box 356)
      - Criticism: Of the U. S. Supreme Court by Presidents of the United States. (Folder empty when processed) (Box Box 356)
      - Lincoln, Abraham: Remarks. (Folder empty when processed) (Box Box 356)
      - Referendum: 1949 May 27, Conducted by Omaha, Nebraska World-Herald, tax, spending, and debt policies (Box Box 356)
      - Richmond News Leader: 1952 July 2, Editorial (Box Box 356)
      - Speeches: On Segregation or Integration, other than Senator Byrd (Box Box 356)
      - Tributes: 1958 February 21 and 24, Paid to Senator Byrd on the floor of the Senate (Box Box 356)
      - Quotations (Box Box 356)
    - 2. Harry Flood Byrd's Speeches
      - Growers-Apple Business, Augusta County, 1920 (Box Box 356)
      - Pay-as-you-go Road Plan vs. Bond Road Plan, 1923 March 20 (Box Box 356)
      - State Democratic Committee Meeting., 1924 (Box Box 356)
      - Presidential Campaign, 1924 (Box Box 356)
      - Acceptance State Democratic Party Chairmanship, 1924 (Box Box 356)
      - Apples - Future in Virginia., 1925 January 28 (Box Box 356)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign, Alexandria., 1925 Summer (Box Box 356)
      - Fall State Tax Program., 1925 (Box Box 356)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign - Keynote Speech, Harrisonburg, Virginia, 1925 October (Box Box 356)
      - American Legion - Armistice Day, 1925 (Box Box 356)
      - Banquet of the Charlie Rouss Fire Company, 1925 (Box Box 356)
      - State Democratic Meeting - Gubernatorial, 1925 (Box Box 356)
      - Pledges, 1925 (Box Box 356)
      - Development of Hampton Roads and Virginia: Home of Industry, 1926-1927 (Box Box 357)
      - Inaugural Address, 1926 February 1 (Box Box 357)
      - Taxation - Virginia General Assembly, 1926 February 2 (Box Box 357)
      - Simplification of Government in Virginia General Assembly., 1926 February 3 (Box Box 357)
      - Governor Ritchie Dinner, Jefferson Hotel, Richmond, Virginia, 1926 February (Box Box 357)
      - Radio Speech on securing Shenandoah National Park, 1926 March 4 (Box Box 357)
      - Congratulatory Message sent to the General Assembly by Governor Byrd on closing day of the session, 1926 March 13 (Box Box 357)
      - Jefferson Day Dinner, Mayflower Hotel., 1926 April 13 (Box Box 357)
      - Southern Maryland Society. Baltimore, Md. (Folder empty when processed), 1926 April 15 (Box Box 357)
      - Cape Henry, 1926 May (Box Box 357)
      - Radio Speech - Boy Scout Movement, 1926 June 9 (Box Box 357)
      - Thomas Jefferson, Monticello, 1926 July 5 (Box Box 357)
      - Virginia Home of Industry. Manufacturers' Record, 1926 November 11 (Box Box 357)
      - Introducing Governor Ritchie to General Assembly, 1926 (Box Box 357)
      - On Thomas Jefferson, 1926 (Box Box 357)
      - Completion of Franklin - Murfreesboro Road., 1926 (Box Box 357)
      - Virginia Reorganization, Extra Session, General Assembly, 1927 March 16 (Box Box 357)
      - Extra Session Message - Virginia Reorganization, 1927 March 21 (Box Box 357)
      - To British Delegation visiting Richmond, 1927 May 17 (Box Box 357)
      - Virginia Institute Citizenship and Government, University of Virginia, 1927 May 18 (Box Box 357)
      - To British Delegation visiting Norfolk, Hampton Roads, 1927 May (Box Box 357)
      - Presentation of President Coolidge, Williamsburg, 1927 May (Box Box 357)
      - Madison County 4-H Club (Reorganization), 1927 July 15 (Box Box 357)
      - Virginia Bar Association. Virginia Beach, 1927 August 3 (Box Box 357)
      - Virginia Institute of Public Affairs, University of Virginia, 1927 August 8 (Box Box 357)
      - Welcoming Richard E. Byrd, Richmond, Virginia, 1927 (Box Box 357)
      - Virginia Bankers Association Convention, Virginia Reorganization., 1927 (Box Box 357)
      - Virginia Reorganization, 1927 (Box Box 357)
      - Speech and Memorandum Welcoming Delaware Delegation, 1927 (Box Box 357)
      - Presentation of Flood Portrait to House of Representatives Foreign Affairs Committee, 1927 (Box Box 357)
      - Address to General Assembly on Virginia Government, 1928 January 11 (Box Box 357)
      - Budget Message to the General Assembly, 1928 January 12 (Box Box 357)
      - Address to General Assembly on Progress Program, 1928 January 16 (Box Box 357)
      - Address to General Assembly on Educational System, 1928 January 16 (Box Box 357)
      - Communication to General Assembly on Seafood and County Government, 1928 January 31 (Box Box 357)
      - Speech - Jefferson Hotel, 1928 February 16 (Box Box 357)
      - Discussion of the Amendments Proposed to the Constitution of Virginia, 1928 June 19 (Box Box 357)
      - Institute of Public Affairs - University of Virginia, 1928 June (Box Box 357)
      - Battle Field Dedication - Fredericksburg, 1928 October 20 (Box Box 357)
      - Speech - Presidential Campaign, 1928 (Box Box 357)
      - Shenandoah Park Purchase and Transfer, 1928 (Box Box 357)
      - Thomas Jefferson - University of Virginia, 1928 (Box Box 357)
      - Virginia Progress, 1928 (Box Box 357)
      - Address - Virginia Education Association, 1928 (Box Box 357)
      - Speech - On Virginia, Ohio State Chamber of Commerce, Columbus, Ohio, 1929 March 22 (Box Box 358)
      - Law Enforcement - Women's Club Federation, Suffolk, Virginia, 1929 May 3 (Box Box 358)
      - Commencement - University of Virginia, 1929 June 12 (Box Box 358)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign. Reply to Henry W. Anderson, 1929 June 29 (Box Box 358)
      - Tax Segregation, before Governors' Conference. New London, Conn., 1929 July 17 (Box Box 358)
      - Opening W.R.V.A. 5000 Watt Radio Station, 1929 August 23 (Box Box 358)
      - Virginia Progress - Chattanooga, Tenn., 1929 October 8 (Box Box 358)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign. Goochland Court House, 1929 October 14 (Box Box 358)
      - George Washington. Charlotte, N.C., 1929 October 17 (Box Box 358)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign. Fairfield, Virginia, 1929 October 24 (Box Box 358)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign. Abingdon, Virginia, 1929 October 28 (Box Box 358)
      - Dedication Maury Statue, Richmond, Virginia, 1929 November 11 (Box Box 358)
      - Introducing Governor elect Pollard to Baptist Conference, 1929 November 12 (Box Box 358)
      - Radio Speech to Boy Scouts, 1929 (Box Box 358)
      - Virginia Agriculture Progress, 1929 (Box Box 358)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1929 (Box Box 358)
      - Columbus Statue Dedication, Richmond, Virginia, 1929 (Box Box 358)
      - George Washington, 1929 (Box Box 358)
      - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1929 (Box Box 358)
      - Welcoming New Englanders' Delegation, 1929 (Box Box 358)
      - Message to General Assembly on the State of the Commonwealth, 1930 January 8 (Box Box 358)
      - Message to General Assembly on the Budget, 1930 January (Box Box 358)
      - Apple Business, 1930 August (Box Box 358)
      - Virginia Horticultural Society, 1930 December 3 (Box Box 358)
      - Dedication of Woodrow Wilson Hall, Harrisonburg State Teachers College, 1930 (Box Box 358)
      - Dedication of University of Virginia Stadium, 1930 (Box Box 358)
      - Apple Business, Martinsburg, 1930 (Box Box 358)
      - Elks, Newport News, 1930 (Box Box 358)
      - Resolution by Virginia General Assembly Endorsing Byrd for President, 1932 January 14 (Box Box 358)
      - South Carolina General Assembly, Reorganization. Columbia, S. C., 1932 February 16 (Box Box 358)
      - Tariff and Agricultural Prosperity, Kentucky Legislature., 1932 February 18 (Box Box 358)
      - North Carolina General Assembly, Virginia Progress, 1932 February 24 (Box Box 358)
      - Prohibition Referendum - Jefferson Day Rally, Washington, D. C., 1932 April 13 (Box Box 358)
      - Prohibition, Democrat Women's Club, Philadelphia, 1932 May 18 (Box Box 358)
      - Virginia State Democratic Convention, 1932 June 10 (Box Box 358)
      - Republican Policies, Presidential Campaign, Hampton, Virginia, 1932 October 4 (Box Box 358)
      - Presidential Campaign 1932. Tariff Policy, Bowling Green, 1932 October 10 (Box Box 358)
      - Radio Speech - Taxes and Reorganization, 1932 November 29 (Box Box 358)
      - Virginia Highway Users Association, Roanoke, Virginia, 1932 December 5 (Box Box 358)
      - Reply to Garber on Tariff. Congressional Campaign 1932 (Box Box 358)
      - Memo. Presidential Campaign, 1932 (Box Box 358)
      - Compilation of Political Utterances by Governor Byrd, 1932 (Box Box 358)
      - Suggested Platform Presidential Campaign 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - Platform, Presidential Campaign, 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - Presidential Campaign 1932. Prior to Chicago Convention (Box Box 359)
      - Presidential Campaign 1932. Prior to Chicago Convention (Box Box 359)
      - Radio - Speech as Chairman of Democratic Executive Committee on Finance. Presidential Campaign, 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - Foreign Trade - Presidential Campaign, 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - Young People's Democratic Club of North Carolina, 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - Prohibition, 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - Prohibition Referendum, 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - Resolution - Endorsing 1932 Presidential Nominee and Platform, Presented to Democratic Central Committee of Virginia (Box Box 359)
      - Acknowledging Endorsement for Presidential Nomination, 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - George Mason, Gunston Hall, 1932 (Box Box 359)
      - Radio Speech, 1933 August 27 (Box Box 359)
      - Radio - Constructive Economy in Government (With Henry Morgenthau, Jr.), 1933 August 29 (Box Box 359)
      - Senate Campaign - Reply to Wise, Garber, etc., Chatham, Virginia, 1933 October 16 (Box Box 359)
      - Farm Situation with Jeffersonion Views, 1933 (Box Box 359)
      - Presenting R. Gray Williams to General Assembly. Unveiling Lee Statue, 1933 (Box Box 359)
      - Notes - Bureaucracy, A.A.A. and N.R.A., 1933 (Box Box 359)
      - A.A.A. Amendments, 1933 (Box Box 359)
      - Apples: Growing, Harvesting and Marketing, 1933 (Box Box 359)
      - South Carolina Speech, 1933 (Box Box 359)
      - Radio - Wild Life Conservation, 1934 January 19 (Box Box 359)
      - Radio - "Lee the Man", 1934 January 19 (Box Box 359)
      - "Three Swords of Lee", 1934 April (Box Box 359)
      - Radio Speech - Three A's, 1934 May 28 (Box Box 359)
      - Senate - A.A.A. and Tugwell Appointment, 1934 June 14 (Box Box 359)
      - Bureaucracy and A.A.A., 1934 July 4 (Box Box 359)
      - Trade Agreement Authority, 1934 March (Box Box 359)
      - Suggestions to General Assembly, 1934 (Box Box 359)
      - Tom MacAdams, 1934 (Box Box 359)
      - Introducing Hon. Jas. A. Farley, Veterans Facility Dedication, Roanoke, Va., 1934 (Box Box 359)
      - "Preserving The Nation's Credit" - Senate Speech, 1935 February 20 (Box Box 359)
      - Town Hall, 1935 March 14 (Box Box 359)
      - Radio - Grange. Nation's Credit, 1935 March 16 (Box Box 359)
      - Senate Speech, 1935 March 19 (Box Box 359)
      - Senate - Work-Relief Program, 1935 March 19 (Box Box 359)
      - Notes for Speech - Federal Bond Security Tax Ex., 1935 Spring (Box Box 359)
      - Radio - Amendments to A.A.A., 1935 April 22 (Box Box 359)
      - William and Mary, 1935 June 10 (Box Box 359)
      - Grange Radio, The Constitution, 1935 July 20 (Box Box 360)
      - Virginia's Sound Government, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1935 October 30 (Box Box 360)
      - Fourth of July Celebration, Washington, D. C., 1935 July 4 (Box Box 360)
      - Opposing $4,800,000,000 Public Works, 1935 (Box Box 360)
      - Federal Constitution and the N.R.A., 1935 (Box Box 360)
      - Memorial to Louis Epes, 1936 January 8 (Box Box 360)
      - Grange Radio, 1936 March 21 (Box Box 360)
      - State Democratic Convention, Norfolk, Va., 1936 June 15 (Box Box 360)
      - Virginia Lions' Convention, 1936 July (Box Box 360)
      - Radio - Presidential Campaign, 1936 October 13 (Box Box 360)
      - Presidential Campaign, Staunton, Virginia, 1936 October 28 (Box Box 360)
      - Presidential Campaign, Pulaski, Virginia, 1936 October 30 (Box Box 360)
      - Radio - Government Reorganization, 1937 January 5 (Box Box 360)
      - Radio Forum - "Government Reorganization", 1937 January 11 (Box Box 360)
      - Senate - R.F.C. Extension, 1937 January 15 (Box Box 360)
      - Radio - Grange. Governmental Reorganization, 1937 January 16 (Box Box 360)
      - Radio - Apple Festival, 1937 May 4 (Box Box 360)
      - University of Richmond, Richmond, Virginia, 1937 May 28 (Box Box 360)
      - University of Virginia, 1937 May 28 (Box Box 360)
      - Radio - Grange, 1937 July 17 (Box Box 360)
      - Democratic Campaign. Richmond, Virginia, 1937 October 25 (Box Box 360)
      - Academy of Political Science, New York, N. Y., 1937 November 10 (Box Box 360)
      - Excerpts from 1937 Observations (Box Box 360)
      - Muhlenberg - Lutheran, 1938 January 1 (Box Box 361)
      - Radio - Reorganization, 1938 January 3 (Box Box 361)
      - Senator Glass, 1938 January 5 (Box Box 361)
      - Senate Speech - Reorganization. (Folder empty when processed.), 1938 January 15 (Box Box 361)
      - Radio - National Grange, 1938 January 22 (Box Box 361)
      - Anti-Lynching Bill, 1938 January 26 (Box Box 361)
      - Senate - Reorganization, 1938 March 18 (Box Box 361)
      - Senate - Three Peacetime Records, 1938 June 2 (Box Box 361)
      - Bankers. Leesburg, Virginia, 1938 July 26 (Box Box 361)
      - Massanetta Springs, Virginia, 1938 August 25 (Box Box 361)
      - Young Democrats, Richmond, Virginia, 1938 August 26 (Box Box 361)
      - Honoring Senator Glass, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1938 October 25 (Box Box 361)
      - Massachusetts Federal Taxpayers Association, Boston, Mass., 1938 December 10 (Box Box 361)
      - Radio Forum - Government Spending, 1939 January 16 (Box Box 361)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Staunton, Virginia, 1939 January 24 (Box Box 361)
      - Virginia Retail Hardware Association, Lynchhurg, Virginia, 1939 February 21 (Box Box 361)
      - George Washington's Birthday, Alexandria, Virginia, 1939 February 22 (Box Box 361)
      - Senate - The Opportunity to Reduce Federal Expenditures, 1939 March 17 (Box Box 361)
      - Radio, National Grange - Wanted: A Sound Fiscal Policy, 1939 March 18 (Box Box 361)
      - Postoffice, Berryville, Virginia, 1939 March (Box Box 361)
      - Bridgewater College, 1939 April 3 (Box Box 361)
      - Illinois Manufacturers' Association, Chicago, Ill., 1939 April 25 (Box Box 361)
      - U. S. Chamber of Commerce, Washington, D. C., 1939 May 2 (Box Box 361)
      - Convention of Travelers Protective Association, Norfolk, Virginia, 1939 May 5 (Box Box 361)
      - Senate - On the Farm Bill (not used), 1939 May 12 (Box Box 361)
      - Maryland Committee for Representative Government, Baltimore, Md., 1939 May 17 (Box Box 361)
      - Memorial Day, Gettysburg, Penna., 1939 May 30 (Box Box 361)
      - Randolph-Macon College, Ashland, Virginia, 1939 June 12 (Box Box 361)
      - National Business College, Roanoke, Virginia, 1939 June 24 (Box Box 361)
      - Senate - Social Security Bill, 1939 July 12 (Box Box 361)
      - Senate - Spend-Lend Bill, 1939 July 26 (Box Box 361)
      - Boy Scouts Picnic, Fisher's Hill, Virginia, 1939 August 5 (Box Box 361)
      - Firemen's Convention, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1939 August 10 (Box Box 361)
      - Appomattox, Virginia, 1939 August 15 (Box Box 361)
      - Cloyd's Farm Battlefield, Dublin, Virginia, 1939 August 16 (Box Box 361)
      - Treasurers' Convention, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1939 August 17 (Box Box 361)
      - Massanetta Springs, Virginia, 1939 August 24 (Box Box 362)
      - Young Democrats Roanoke Convention, Roanoke, Virginia, 1939 August 25 (Box Box 362)
      - American Legion Convention, Richmond, Virginia, 1939 August 28 (Box Box 362)
      - Editoral - Senator Byrd, 1939 October 6 (Box Box 362)
      - Richmond Civic Clubs, Richmond, Virginia, 1939 November 7 (Box Box 362)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1939 November 8 (Box Box 362)
      - Remarks in New Market, 1939 November 10 (Box Box 362)
      - Presenting Postmaster General Farley, Winchester, Virginia, 1939 November 17 (Box Box 362)
      - State Horticultural Society Meeting, Roanoke, Virginia, 1939 December 6 (Box Box 362)
      - Tidewater Grocers, 1939 (Box Box 362)
      - Senator Glass' birthday, Sweet Briar College, 1940 January 4 (Box Box 362)
      - Jackson Day Dinner, Richmond, Virginia, 1940 January 15 (Box Box 362)
      - Jackson Day Dinner, Alexandria, Virginia, 1940 January 18 (Box Box 362)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1940 January 19 (Box Box 362)
      - Introducing Senator Wheeler to the Virginia Press Association, Richmond, Virginia, 1940 January 27 (Box Box 362)
      - Keel-Laying of Battleship Alabama, Portsmouth, Va., 1940 February 1 (Box Box 362)
      - Reopening Norfolk-Portsmouth Bridge, 1940 February 1 (Box Box 362)
      - Baltimore Real Estate Board, Baltimore, Md., 1940 February 10 (Box Box 362)
      - Winchester, Virginia, 1940 March 12 (Box Box 362)
      - Women's Clubs, Danville, Virginia, 1940 March 13 (Box Box 362)
      - Danville Civic Clubs - Tobacco, Danville, Virginia, 1940 March 13 (Box Box 362)
      - Hampton Roads Maritime Exchange, 1940 March 14 (Box Box 362)
      - Masonic Dinner, Arlington, Virginia, 1940 March 16 (Box Box 362)
      - Senate - Treasury Balance, 1940 March 19 (Box Box 362)
      - Senate - Soil Conservation Payments, 1940 March 20 (Box Box 362)
      - Senate - Treasury's working balance. Deposits of governmental corporations, 1940 March 22 (Box Box 362)
      - Joint Meeting of Civic Clubs of Roanoke, Roanoke, Virginia, 1940 March 28 (Box Box 362)
      - Senate - Parity payments. (Not delivered), 1940 March (Box Box 362)
      - City Employees Beneficial Association, Norfolk, Virginia, 1940 April 22 (Box Box 362)
      - School Celebration, Amelia Court House, Va., 1940 May 3 (Box Box 362)
      - American Pharmacautical Association, Richmond, Virginia, 1940 May 8 (Box Box 362)
      - National Defense Appropriations, 1940 May 22 (Box Box 362)
      - Senate - National Defense. Senator's plan for meeting necessities of national defense, 1940 May 28 (Box Box 362)
      - Tribute to Hon. J. Edgar Hoover, 1940 May 31 (Box Box 362)
      - Annual Convention of Virginia Association of Insurance Agents, Virginia Beach, Virginia, 1940 June 1 (Box Box 362)
      - Fork Union Military Academy, Fork Union, Virginia, 1940 June 3 (Box Box 362)
      - Benedictine High School, Richmond, Virginia, 1940 June 11 (Box Box 362)
      - Democratic State Convention, Roanoke, Virginia, 1940 June 14 (Box Box 362)
      - Radio Forum - Financial Defense, 1940 June 17 (Box Box 362)
      - Senate - 10 Reduction in Appropriations, 1940 June 18 (Box Box 362)
      - Young Democrats, Alexandria, Virginia, 1940 July 27 (Box Box 362)
      - Lantz Mills, Virginia, 1940 August 10 (Box Box 362)
      - Dedication Hebron Lutheran Church, Madison County, Virginia, 1940 August 24 (Box Box 362)
      - Senate - Tax Bill. Tax Exempt Securities, 1940 September 14 (Box Box 362)
      - Senate Remarks - Recessing for 3 day period. (Barkley), 1940 October 9 (Box Box 362)
      - Tribute to Mr. M. M. Lynch, Winchester, Virginia, 1940 (Box Box 362)
      - Retirement Bill. Amendment to H. R. 3487, 1941 January 19 (Box Box 363)
      - Senate - Debt Limit, Fiscal Conditions etc. Present and Post-War Problems, 1941 February 14 (Box Box 363)
      - Senate - Amendment Lend-Lease Bill, 1941 March 5 (Box Box 363)
      - Strikes in Defense Industries, 1941 March 27 (Box Box 363)
      - Jackson Day, Richmond, Virginia, 1941 March (Box Box 363)
      - Agricultural Appropriation Bill, 1941 April 2 (Box Box 363)
      - Strikes, 1941 April 2 (Box Box 363)